<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
<entry key="dss_applet_section">Sign the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_section_sign_extern_ol">Sign the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_section_desc">You must sign the PDF form electronically in order to submit it by electronic means to the court</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_section_sign_extern_ol_desc">You must sign the PDF form electronically in order to submit it by electronic means to the court</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_methods_desc">How do you want to sign your document?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_lnk_help">Need help with this page? Follow this link.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_select_1_method">Please select one of the following options.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_sc">Sign using a card</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_sc">Use this option to sign your document with a card or a USB device that you plug into your computer. The software that is specific to your card or device must be properly installed on your computer. Please make sure that your card reader is connected to your computer.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_java_needed">You must have Java installed to use this option. Java does not work in Microsoft Edge and in Google Chrome version 45 and higher.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_ext">Sign using a third party application or service</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_ext">This option allows you to download and sign the document by another electronic means.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_eoss">Sign using an online service</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_eoss">Select a service from the list of services supported by this web site.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_ampss">Sign using your mobile phone (only for holders of an Austrian Bürgerkarte)</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_ampss">Choose this option if you have an Austrian Bürgerkarte and you want to use your mobile phone to sign the document. You will be redirected to the A-Trust website for signing.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_show_advanced_methods">Advanced options [(click here to display them…)]</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_please_select_method">Please select a signing method.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_advanced_methods">Advanced options</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_installed_cert">Sign using a certificate stored in the Windows operating system</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_installed_cert">Use this option to sign your document with a certificate stored in the Windows operating system certificate store.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_p12">Sign using a certificate file (.p12)</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_method_descr_p12">Use this option if your certificate is stored in a .p12 file located on your hard drive or on a USB key.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_javascript_needed">You must enable JavaScript to use this option.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_test_page_header">Test your digital signature</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_choose_sign_method">Proceed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_choose_sign_method_desc">Click here to go to the page where you can sign your document. You will be able to review the document before signing it.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_redirect_to_no_java_link">Please wait while the Java applet loads or [click here] to continue without running the Java applet.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_other_sign_option_title">click here</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_showOpenSealedPdfTitle">Review the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_prompt_openSealedPdf">Please make sure you review the PDF form before you sign it. Do you want to open the PDF form now?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_yes">Yes</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_no">No</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_other_sign_option">If you want to select another signing option, [click here].</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_certificates_no_certs">No certificates found.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_advice_no_card_detected">We did not detect a card connected to this computer. Please make sure your card reader is connected and that the card is properly inserted in the reader.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_advice_jre6_link">I don't see my certificate here.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_you_will_sign_with">You will sign with certificate:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_show_other_certs">Let me choose a different certificate</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_sign_desc">Click this button to sign the PDF form with the selected signing certificate:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sign">Sign the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_sign_input_tt">Sign the PDF form with the selected certificate</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_refresh">Read card(s) again</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_refresh_tt">Read the certificates from the card(s) again</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sign_test">Test your signature</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_certs_refreshed">The certificates list has been reloaded.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_card_detection_unavailable">Automatic detection of the card is not possible.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_more_than_one_card">We have detected more than one card connected to your computer. We recommend that you remove the card(s) that you do not intend to sign the PDF form with, and click the "Read card(s) again" button.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_smartcard_removed">The card has been removed since the certificates were loaded. Please re-insert your card, click the "Read card(s) again" button, and try again.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_use_os_cert_store">We detected a card connected to your computer. The list of certificates may contain certificates from the card.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signedpdf_ok_test">Signature test successful. Please close this page to continue with your claim.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pdf_path">The PDF form is temporarily stored at {0}.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_test_page_text">This is a sample PDF to help you test your electronic signature.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_please_wait">Loading … please wait.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_proceed_ampss">Click the "Proceed" button to send your form to the online signature service you selected.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_btn_proceed">Proceed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_signature_cancelled">You cancelled the signing process in the online signature service.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_parse_error">The online signature service gave an invalid response. Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_response_timeout">The online signature service did not respond. Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_format_invalid">The format of the digital signature is not valid. Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_error_code">There was an error in the online signature service. Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_click_to_refresh">If this page does not refresh automatically after 30 seconds, please [click here].</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_eoss_error_load">An error occurred during the preparation of your document. Please click the "Back" button below to try again.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_pkcs12_desc">Please locate your certificate file</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_browse">Browse …</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_pkcs12_browse_tt">Open the file containing your certificate</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_requestPasswordTitle">Password or PIN Entry</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_provide_password">Provide password or PIN</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_why_password_pkcs12">The application needs the password for the certificates file you have selected in order to list the certificates that are available for signing. If you want to allow this, enter your password or PIN below and click OK. Otherwise, just click Cancel.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_why_password_card">The application needs to access your card in order to list the certificates that are available for signing. If you want to allow this, enter your password or PIN below and click OK. Otherwise, just click Cancel.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_why_password_card_mocca">The application needs to access your card in order to sign digitally. If you want to allow this, enter your password or PIN below and click OK. Otherwise, just click Cancel and the PDF form will not be signed.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_txt_password_desc">Password or PIN</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_ok">OK</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_cancel">Cancel</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_wrong_pin">Your PIN or password is not valid. Remember that you can block your card if you enter the wrong PIN too many times.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_wrong_pin_mocca">Your PIN or password is not valid. Remember that you can block your card if you enter the wrong PIN too many times.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_pin_pad_entry">PIN Pad Entry</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_why_password_mocca_pin_pad">In order to sign the form, please enter your PIN on your PIN pad.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_wrong_pin_mocca_pin_pad">Your PIN is not valid. Remember that you can block your card if you enter the wrong PIN too many times.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_issued_to">Issued To</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_issued_by">Issued By</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_serial_no">Serial Number</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_valid_from">Valid From</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_valid_to">Valid To</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_certificate_summary_issuer_statement">Issuer Statement</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_certificates_desc">Which certificate do you want to use for signing?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_certificates_recommended_desc">Certificate(s) recommended for signing:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_certificates_other_desc">Other certificate(s) on this computer:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sel_certificates_other_no_recommend_desc">Certificate(s) on this computer:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pin_entry_cancelled">The PIN entry was cancelled.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pin_entry_cancelled_mocca">The PIN entry was cancelled.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pkcs12_path">The certificates were read from the file {0}.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_wrong_pkcs12_file">The selected file does not contain a certificate. You may have selected the wrong file.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signedpdf_ok">The signed PDF form has been uploaded successfully. Please click Next to continue with the submission of your claim.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signed">You have signed the PDF form with certificate {0}.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_different_certificate">If you want to sign with a different certificate, [click here].</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_download_signed_desc">Click this button if you want to save a copy of the signed PDF form to your computer:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_download_pdf">Download the signed PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_download_signed_input_tt">Download a copy of the PDF form that you have just signed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pdf_saved_path">The PDF form was saved to the file {0}.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pdf_not_saved">The file could not be saved to {0}. Please check that you are allowed to save to that location or if the file is opened by another application.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_session_expired">Your session has expired.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sessionExpiredTitle">Session Expired</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_prompt_session_expired">Your session has expired. Do you want to save your PDF form?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_appletInitialisationFailureTitle">Initialisation Failure</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_bug_java_version_applet">Your Java version is not supported with current security settings. The application will exit. Please consult the help page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_showUnsupportedVendorTitle">Unsupported Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_unsupported_vendor">Your browser uses the OpenJDK plugin, however our signing service requires the Oracle Java plugin. Please install the latter and configure your browser to use it in order to access the signing service.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_warning">Warning</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_cert_date_invalid">The selected certificate has expired or is not yet valid. Are you sure you want to use it?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_overwrite_file_title">Confirm replace file</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_overwrite_file">The file already exists. Do you want to replace it?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_download_ol_desc">Download the PDF form to be signed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_download_pdf_ol">Download the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_view_pdf">View the PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_upload_signed_ol_desc">Please digitally sign the form you downloaded without changing it in any way before you do so. Then locate the file containing the signed PDF form on your computer and click the "Upload the signed PDF form" button below to upload it to the European e-Justice Portal</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_upload_signed_pdf">Upload the signed PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_upload_pdf_ol">Upload the signed PDF form</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_upload_browse_tt">Upload the PDF form that you have digitally signed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_status_warning">You have signed the PDF form successfully, but your digital signature may not be accepted by the court because:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_status_error">Your digital signature cannot be accepted by the European e-Justice Portal because:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_cert_expired">The signing certificate has expired or is not yet valid.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_not_trusted">We could not establish that your signing certificate is a trusted certificate: certificate providers must respect strict standards in order for the signing certificates they issue to be legally valid within the European Union. We have not been able to verify that your certificate provider has met these strict standards. For more help, please contact your certificate provider and ask if they are compliant with the European legislation on electronic signatures.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signature_invalid">We could not establish that your signing certificate is still valid. To check validity we depend on your certificate provider to operate a service that allows us to confirm that your certificate was not revoked. It may be that this service is (temporarily) unavailable. Please contact your certificate provider for more information.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pdf_not_signed">You have not signed the PDF form.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_uploaded_pdf_tampered">The uploaded PDF form was changed after it was signed.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_uploaded_pdf_not_in_workflow">The uploaded PDF form does not correspond to the data you have entered in the European e-Justice portal. Have you selected the correct file?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_uploaded_pdf_not_from_server">The uploaded PDF form is not the one provided by the European e-Justice Portal.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signed_before_seal">The date and time of your signature is before the date and time the document was created</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_signed_pdf_not_uploaded">The signed PDF has not been uploaded.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_uploaded_pdf_ok">The uploaded PDF form is valid.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_technical_failure">There was a technical error in the digital signing service.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_controller_error">There was a technical error in the digital signing service (component: controller).</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_prompt_to_download_java">You do not have Java installed on your computer or your Java version is too old, or your browser is not configured to use Java. To sign your form using the method you chose you need to install Java and/or configure your browser to use it. After doing so, you may have to restart your browser. If you decide to proceed with the installation of Java, you will be prompted to save the data you filled in. We strongly recommend that you do this so that you can later reload it using the "Load electronically signed PDF" functionality of the European e-Justice Portal.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_install_java_save_sign_online">Install Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_install_java_save_sign_online_tt">Install Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_dont_install_java_sign_offline">Do not install Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_dont_install_java_sign_offline_tt">Do not install Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_java_configured">I have now configured my browser to use Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_java_configured_tt">I have now configured my browser to use Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_bug_java_version">We strongly advise you to upgrade your Java plugin to the latest version before you sign the form electronically. If you decide to proceed with the upgrade of Java, you will be prompted to save the data you filled in. We strongly recommend that you do this so that you can later reload it using the "Load electronically signed PDF" functionality of the European e-Justice Portal. If you are unable to upgrade your Java plugin, [a highly discouraged workaround] that puts your machine at risk is possible.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_here_to_proceed">[Click here to proceed] once the workaround is in place (insecure).</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_here_to_proceed_title">Click here to proceed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_btn_back">Back</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_install_java">Upgrade Java</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_not_scriptable">There is a problem with your Java configuration; [click here] to read the troubleshooting guide.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mac_unsafe">In order to use this service you must allow your browser to view this website in "unsafe" mode; [click here] to read how you can do that in our troubleshooting guide.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_sec_download_java_mac_chrome">The Chrome browser does not support the Java plug-in on Mac. We recommend that you to use the Safari or Firefox browser instead.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_long_operation">Please wait. The operation can take several minutes to complete</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_password_dialog_hidden">A box for you to enter a password or PIN may be "behind" your browser!</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_insert_card">There may be a window "behind" your browser asking you to insert a card - please close that window to continue. You may need to repeat this multiple times.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_errorReportTitle">Error Report</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_error_report_desc">There was a technical error in the digital signing service. The details of the error are displayed below. In order to improve our service to you we kindly ask you to send these details to us by clicking the Yes button.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_show_error_report_details">Show the error details</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_error_report_agree">Do you agree to provide this information?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_error_report_thanks">Thank you for providing the error report. We will analyse this and hope to improve our service to you in future.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_title_upload_log">Technical Information</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_intro_upload_log">To improve our service, would like to upload the following technical information about how you used this page:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_ask_upload_log">Do you agree to provide this information?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_showAppletDeathTitle">Application Error</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_death">Unfortunately, the application has closed unexpectedly. We apologise for the inconvenience.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_death_link">Click here to restart the application.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_showSurveyTitle">User Feedback</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_survey_desc">The PDF form was successfully signed and uploaded. In order to improve our service we would like to record the technical details of how you signed the PDF. None of this information can personally identify you. The information we would collect is the following:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_survey_issuer_desc">Please also provide the name of the organisation that issued the card (or other signing device) you used:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_survey_agree">Do you agree to provide this information?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_user_survey_thanks">Thank you for providing the technical details of your signature! This will help us improve our service to you and other users.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_tampered_communication">We detected that the communication channel between your browser and the European e-Justice Portal is insecure. To ensure your security, the signing application has closed automatically. Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp1Title">You don't see your signing certificate</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_1_1">In order to sign with your card, you need to have software that is specific to your card installed on your computer.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_1_2">Is this software installed on your computer?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_1_yes">Yes</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_1_no">No</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_1_dunno">I don't know</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp2Title">Install software</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_2_1">You must download and install the software specific to your card from the website of the issuer of your card.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_2_2">By clicking on "Proceed with download and installation" below, you will be prompted to save the data you filled in. We strongly recommend that you do this so that you can later reload it using the "Load electronically signed PDF" functionality of the European e-Justice Portal.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_redirect_to_issuer">You will then be redirected to a website that will provide you with more information about your card.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_2_4">After you have installed the software (you may be asked to restart your computer), please try again to sign. If you still do not see your certificate, run this help tool one more time.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_click_here_down">Proceed with download and installation</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_2_proceed">Proceed with download and installation</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp3Title">You don't know if the required software is installed</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_3_1">Using a card requires to have specific software installed, which is usually not installed by default. Therefore, if you have never used your card on this computer before, it probably means that you don't have this software installed.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_3_2">Did you use your card on this computer before?</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mw_3_yes">Yes</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mw_3_no">No</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp5Title">Provide software location</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_pkcs11_desc">We were not able to use the software to read your card. It is possible that services supporting your card are not running. If you have other software that can read your card, please try to use that to confirm that you card works at the moment, and then try our service again.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_pkcs11_desc_2">Alternatively, you can provide us with the location of this software (a "PKCS11" library file) and we can try to use that to read your card.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_file_pkcs11_desc_windows">Please note that on a Windows computer, the installed software normally just works and it is usually not necessary to use a "PKCS11" library file, but maybe your computer has a special configuration.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_library_path">Library Path:</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_folder">Folder or</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_wrong_pkcs11_lib">The selected PKCS11 library does not correspond to the inserted card.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_pkcs11_path">The PKCS11 library was loaded from the file {0}.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp4Title">Sorry</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_4_1">Please contact the Portal administrator through the 'Your feedback' page or try to sign your document by other means.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_mwHelp6Title">Open card provider website</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_message_mw_6_1">Please consult your card issuer's website to obtain the required software.</entry>
<entry key="dss_applet_operation_cancelled">The operation was interrupted by the user.</entry>

</properties>